# **Software Engineer**

# JAMIE LEVINER

 $\checkmark$ 

levinerjamie@gmail.com

**U** (843) 229-

1193

jamieleviner.com

**G** jamieleviner

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **ACS Technologies**

**Software Engineer** | July 2017 - present

Programming and watching cute cat videos.

## **ACS Technologies**

**Software Engineer-Associate** | July 2016 - July 2017

Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

#### **ACS Technologies**

**Software Development Apprentice |** August 2015 - July 2016

Making coffee and baking cookies.

#### **ACS Technologies**

**Intern |** May 2015 - August 2016

## **EDUCATION**

## Francis Marion University, Florence, SC 29501

**B.S. in Computer Science, Minor in Applied Mathematics** | January

2011 - December 2014

## **SKILLS**

- JavaScript
- jQuery
- VueJS

- CSS/LESS/SASS
- C#/ASP.NET MVC
- Go

- Intercom
- PostgreSQL

# **About me**

For the past 5 years, I have worked as a full stack software engineer with a concentration on front-end architecture, frameworks, and tooling. I am strongly interested in becoming part of a development culture that improves and enables its people, and I am looking forward to facing some new challenges.